JURAEV NOSIRJON

Contact

Address:

88 Faywood Blvd, North York, ON M3H 2X4

Phone:

+1 437 972 5665

Email:

juraevca@gmail.com

Website:

https://juraevca.github.io/

Languages

English – Fluent

Summary

A well-educated, experienced economist, econometrician, data engineer and full-stack developer with solid programming skills and a proven record of leadership.

Skill Highlights

Technical skills: PHP, Javascript, Python, MySQL, CSS, GraphQL, HTML, Eviews, Matlab, SASS, Stata, Scripting languages (powershell, bash), Git

Soft skills: analytical skills, good communicator, critical thinker, detailoriented, can write good reports, goal-oriented

Experience

Head of Distance Learning Division - 03/2022 to Present *Agrobank JSCB, Tashkent, UZB*

Senior Data Engineer - 08/2021 to 03/2022 *Agrobank JSCB, Tashkent, UZB*

Data Scientist - 07/2019 to 07/2020 Induci Inc., FL, USA

Teaching Assistant - 07/2019 to 07/2020 *Louisiana State University, LA, USA*

Data Analyst - 05/2014 to 08/2019
"DAVYERGEODEZKADASTR" Land Management
and Real Estate Cadaster, Andizhan, UZB

Education

Graduate Certificate Diploma: **Advanced Econometrics** - 2018 **Louisiana State University**, LA, USA

Master of Science (M.Sc.): **Economics** - 2017 **Louisiana State University**, LA, USA

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.): **Economics and Finance** - 2014 **Westminster International University in Tashkent** (accredited to the

University of Westminster in London, UK), Tashkent, UZB